# **Dmitrii** Lisin

## Software Programmer, Embedded Programmer

190000, Saint Petersburg, Saint Petersburg RU

@mrlisdim (https://t.me/mrlisdim)

in dmitrii-lisin (https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmitrii-lisin/)



Since childhood, I've been in love with programming. When I began my career as an intern at an electronics design firm, I discovered that I enjoyed creating something that worked in real life rather than just inside my computer. I have finished a lot of embedded projects from different spheres and dealt with numerous instruments, protocols, and peripherals. It has always been my intention to write only high-quality, human-readable code. Had prior team leadership experience, but preferred to work as an equal member of the team. In my free time, I also prefer to extend my knowledge of programming languages, techniques, and trends by working with hobby projects.

#### SKILLS

#### **Embedded Development Python Development** CI/CD Master Advanced Intermediate C/C++ | Zephyr | FreeRTOS | STM32 | FastAPI | Pydantic | ORM | Docker | Docker Compose | Nordic | Real-time protocols | WAMP protocol | Async | Threading Github Actions | Gitlab Pipelines Industrial protocols | Stack only programming Common **Web Development** Rust Intermediate Beginner VSC | Gitlab | Github | Reviewing | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Typescript | Tauri Linux | Reading schematics | React | Parcel | Rollup Datasheet exploring

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020 - Current

Team leader at LLC "Third Pin"

Developed a flexible testing system for embedded electronics based on distributed micro-services connected by PubSub/RPC Web-protocol.

- Robster: flexible testing system for electronic devices (Python, WAMP, Microservice, Docker, PostgreSQL)
- Gate valve controller (ARM, STM32, Zephyr, Modbus)
- GPS tracker for a professional training (ARM, Nordic, GPS, UBlox, Ant)

2013 - 2020

### Embedded Software Developer at LLC "Third Pin"

Have been finished more than 20 commercial projects in embedded area including IoT, safety systems, shipbuilding.

- Pastilda: hardware password manager (STM32, ARM, Crypto Peripheral, SDIO, FatFS, FreeRTOS)
- Ship ruder control system (ARM, STM32, USB HID, FreeRTOS)
- Fire alarm system (ARM, STM32)
- MTUTA: Telemetry of vending machines (ARM, FreeRTOS, USB, SD, SIMCom, GSM, Ethernet, FTP)

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Pastilda**

2016 - 2017

team/pastilda) https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin\_team/pastilda (https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin\_team/pastilda)

Skills acquired: C++ | Embedded | Open-source

Open-source hardware designed to manage our credentials in handy and secure way.

#### Just Run My Debugger!

2021 - Current

Ithtps://github.com/ila-embsys/justrunmydebugger (https://github.com/ila-embsys/justrunmydebugger)

Skills acquired: Rust | Rescript | Tauri | React

Pet project, simple GUI for OpenOCD debugger.

#### **EDUCATION**

 $\textbf{Master Intelligent Technologies in Robotics} \text{ at } \mathsf{ITMO} \text{ University}$ 

2016 - 2018

Bachelor Intelligent Technologies in Robotics at ITMO University

2012 - 2016

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** Russian
Fluent Native Speaker

#### **INTERESTS**

Games Books Traveling

**Hobby programming** 

#### **REFERENCES**

" ... "

Ivan Larionov, LLC "Third Pin" CEO